

Jyotirmayi Swain

Phone number: (+49) 15124884481 (Mobile) | **Email address:**

jyotirmayi.swain@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

A Frontend Engineer **2.5 years of Frontend web development** experience **specializing** in **React JS with Typescript**. Currently learning **Next JS** to keep myself updated with **latest Web Development** updates. My portfolio Link --** https://jvoti28490.github.io/ **

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/07/2022 - 31/10/2023 Gummersbach, Germany

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (FRONTEND) MODIS

- Development of modern frontends for web applications with a special focus on the user experience
- Focus on code quality following best practices of React.js
- Responsibility for the development of SPA frontend
- Developing new features to meet customer requirements
- Bring existing features up to date with the latest technology
- · Close exchange with the UI/UX team, operational teams and business stakeholders

11/12/2021 - 30/06/2022 Germany

LOOKING FOR OPPORTUNITIES OPEN TO WORK

Looking for opportunities in Germany after moving in November 2021 (**Family reunion**) and **updating myself** with the **latest technology** in **frontend** by **learning** from **video tutorials**.

02/10/2019 - 20/11/2021 Bangalore, India

TECHNOLOGY ANALYST TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES

- Design and develop responsive, web Applications
- Render data from different API endpoints
- Collaborate closely with development team to deliver high value to the end-user

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

17/06/2008 - 17/06/2012 Bhubaneswar, India

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY IN ELECTRONICS AND TELECOMMUNICATION Biju Patnaik University of Technology

2012-2014: Preparation for GATE Exam

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Other language(s):

| | UNDERSTANDING | | SPEAKING | | WRITING |
|---------|---------------|---------|----------------------|-----------------------|---------|
| | Listening | Reading | Spoken production | Spoken interaction | |
| ENGLISH | C2 | C2 | C2 | C2 | C2 |
| GERMAN | A2 | A2 | A2 | A2 | A2 |

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user